thefwoosh.com 2016-06-23

# About | The Fwoosh

### [](http://i0.wp.com/thefwoosh.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/05/fwoosh_watermark.png)

### Site Description

With over fifteen thousand registered users, thefwoosh.com is one of the most popular website communities for action figure collectors and customizers. Each month, the site has nearly 120,000 unique visitors, generating nearly 400,000 site visits and 4.5 million pageviews.

While the majority of visitors are from the United States, thefwoosh.com’s reach is global, with regular visitors from 88 countries. In terms of visits, the top ten countries after the United States are: Canada, the United Kingdom, Australia, Brazil, Singapore, Mexico, the Netherlands, the Philippines, Germany, and France.

While thefwoosh.com does not collect demographic information on its visitors, anecdotal information places the age range from early teens to mid-forties, predominantly male. The most heavily represented category would be males from 18 – 34 years of age.

* * *

### Advertising

Please direct all advertising-related inquiries to [promotions@thefwoosh.com](mailto:promotions@thefwoosh.com).

* * *

### Staff

#### Site Administrators

**pablolobo** (Paul Wolf) | CEO and Founder  
---|---  
**RoboKillah** (Brian Rutherford) | Chief Operating Officer  
**Industrial** (Adam Van Wickler) | Chief Brand Officer / Creative Director  
**VeeBee** (Nic Wood) | Chief Content Officer / Editor In Chief  
  
#### Forum Moderators

**ActorJez** (John Jezior) | All Forums  
---|---  
**canonball** (Timothy Pittz) | All Forums  
**carl** (Scott Akers) | All Forums  
**DisThunder** (Dustin Downey) | All Forums  
**Ibentmyman-thing** (Daniel Wilson) | All Forums  
**Matthew K** (Matthew Kloberdanz) | All Forums  
**Prodigy** (Brett Gaillot) | All Forums  
**Tenbones** | All Forums  
**Tommyboy1972** | All Forums  
  
#### Front Page Staff

**VeeBee** (Nic Wood) | Editor in Chief / Publisher  
---|---  
**canonball** (Timothy Pittz) | Managing Editor  
**Ibentmyman-thing** (Daniel Wilson) | Editor  
**Matthew K** (Matthew Kloberdanz) | Editor/Lead Photographer  
****RoboKillah**  **(Brian Rutherford) **  
** | Writer  
**Prodigy** (Brett Gaillot) | Writer  
**hagop** (Tony Hagopian) **  
** | Writer/Reporter  
**themanintheanthill** (Jason R. Mink) | Writer  
**Ladybug** (L. Crowl) | Writer  
**fireball13z** (Matt Stein) | Writer  
**snowman** | Writer  
**JKL-MD ReFugee** (Jeffery K. Lyles) | Writer  
**BCR Duke  **(Brian Charles Rooney) | Writer  
**DisThunder** (Dustin Downey) | Writer  
  
### Fwooshcast Members

hagop (Tony Hagopian) |  Host  
---|---  
VeeBee (Nic Wood) |  Co-Host and windbag  
|   
  
### FwooshTube

 Robokillah (Brian Rutherford) |  Reviewer  
---|---  
 VeeBee (Nic Wood) |  Reviewer  
canonball (Timothy Pittz) | Reviewer  
  
* * *

### Forum Rules

Please abide by the following rules while visiting thefwoosh.com.  Folks who break the rules will be subject to a site ban.

  1. **No personal attacks of any kind** – treat all members and guests with respect.
  2. **Keep it PG** – we’re a toy site, and we have kid members.
  3. **No leaked pictures** – discussion of items you’ve seen elsewhere is fine, but we have several members and regular guests from various toy companies and respect their intellectual property.
  4. **No spam** , including but not limited to – advertisements of toy-related stores or customs commissions, affiliated linking within the forum, post count bumps, thread bumps, duplicate posts in a thread, and duplicate posts across boards.
  5. **TheFwoosh.com reserves the right to remove any content (posts, images, avatars, signatures, and anything else you might be able to put up) at our sole discretion.**

* * *

### Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to TheFwoosh.com is important to us.

At TheFwoosh.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit TheFwoosh.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

#### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
